# ABHIJIT HANUMANT JADHAV

abhijit.jadhav1998@gmail.com

🕻 +91 8446755971 Pune, Maharashtra, India



<u>GitHub</u>







# **CAREER SUMMARY**

1.6+ years of Full Stack development experience as a Java Developer in the analysis, design, implementation, integration, testing, and maintenance of applications using Java. Extensively worked on ERP with good knowledge of developing complex projects and good management skills of the deliverables.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE



# Accenture Application Development Analyst December 2020 To Present (1.6 Year )

- Worked on agile scrum methodology and involved in standup meetings to monitor the progress.
- Involved in requirement gathering, analysis, design, optimization, and documentation of the application.
- Implementing full-stack application using Spring boot, Spring MVC, Spring Security, Spring Data JPA, and Web services.
- Writing various Unit testing Junit and Mockito test cases.
- Time Entry workflow optimization on ERP to handle more number of users at the same time with limited server resources.
- Worked on Inactive user Automation and PS Level Restriction Automation on ERP.
- Member of MyExperience team responsible for arranging Team building events at DU Level.

# **INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCE**



Persistent Systems
Software Engineer Intern
January 2019 To June 2019 (6 Months)

- Interview Automation on an online campus test conducting platform called CodeSlash.
- Integrated the automation module with the application enabling the feature of conducting the interview on the platform.
- Designed and Developed the workflow of the Admin side, User side, and evaluator side.
- Integration and unit testing of the application
- Improve the code quality by implementing best practices.

# **OPEN SOURCE CONTRIBUTIONS**

- Contributor to cartoonizer web Deep learning application.
- Technical blogger at Medium.
- Content writer at GeekforGeeks.
- Published "Deepfake Video Detection using Neural Networks", International Journal for Scientific Research and Development,04 April 2020

# **SKILLS**

#### **FRONT END**

React, HTML, CSS, JavaScript

## **BACK END**

Java, SpringBoot, Microservice, Python for AI

#### **DATABASE**

MYSOL

#### **UNIT TESTING**

JUnit, Mockito Framework

#### **DEVOPS**

Docker, Kubernetes

#### **OTHERS**

Deep Learning, Data Structures and Algorithms

#### **PROJECT**

- DeepFake Video Detection
- AI-Based Attendance System
- Railway Reservation System
- Todo Microservice Full-stack React app

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Master Microservices with Spring Boot and Spring Cloud By Udemy
- Deep Learning Specialization from deeplearning.ai on Coursera
- Infosys Certified Software Programmer through InfyTQ
- Go Java Full Stack with Spring Boot and React by Udemy
- Full Stack Automation Engineer certified by Accenture
- DevOps for Java and Spring Boot

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Boards of Studies Member at G. H Raisoni College of Engineering and Management, Pune
- 1st Rank Second Year, Third Year, Fourth Year in B.Tech

# **EDUCATION**

- B.Tech Computer Engineering | CGPA: 9.80
   | G. H Raisoni College of Engineering and Management, Pune (2016 – 2020)
- AISSCE | Percentage: 62.2%
   Army Public School, Kirkee (March 2016)
- AISSE | CGPA: 9.19 | Army Public School, Chandimandir(March 2014)